rentmanager.com 2015-06-10

# Privacy Statement

## What this Privacy Statement covers

This policy covers how London Computer Systems, Inc. (LCS) treats personal information that LCS collects and receives, including information related to your past use of LCS products and services. Personal information is information about you that is personally identifiable like your name, address, email address, or phone number, and that is not otherwise publicly available.

This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that LCS does not own or control, or to people that LCS does not employ or manage. In addition, certain LCS associated channel partners and partners have their own privacy statements.

* * *

## Information collection and use

### General

LCS collects personal information when you register with LCS, when you use LCS products or services, when you visit LCS pages or the pages of certain LCS partners, and when you enter promotions or request newsletters. LCS may combine information about you that we have with information we obtain from business partners or other companies.

When you register we ask for information such as your name, email address, company name, phone numbers, fax numbers, street addresses, and general company information. For some financial products and services we may also ask for your address, credit card number, and information about your assets. Once you register with LCS and sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us.

LCS collects information about your transactions with us and with some of our business partners, including information about your use of financial products and services that we offer.

LCS automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address, LCS cookie information, and the page you request.

LCS uses information for the following general purposes: to customize the advertising, fulfill your requests for products and services, improve our services, contact you, and conduct research.

* * *

## Information Sharing and Disclosure

LCS does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or nonaffiliated companies except to provide products or services you've requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances.

We provide the information to trusted partners who work on behalf of or with LCS under confidentiality agreements. These companies may use your personal information to help LCS communicate with you about offers from LCS and our marketing partners. However, these companies do not have any independent right to share this information.

We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims;

We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of LCS's terms of use, or as otherwise required by law.

We transfer information about you if LCS is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, LCS will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

LCS works with vendors, partners, advertisers, and other service providers in different industries and categories of business.

* * *

## Your ability to edit and delete your Account Information and Preferences

### General

You may request to have your information changed or removed at anytime however doing so will prevent LCS from offering you new products and hinder efforts to support the products and services you may have purchased.

### Confidentiality and Security

We limit access to personal information about you to employees who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs.

We have physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with federal regulations to protect personal information about you.

### Changes to this Privacy Policy

LCS may update this policy. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your LCS account or by placing a prominent notice on our site.

### Questions and Suggestions

If you have questions or suggestions, please email us at info@rentmanager.com or call us at 513-583-1482.
